{
    "subject": "resource/Madame_Butterfly_(1915_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/writer",
    "object": "resource/John_Luther_Long",
    "human_readable": "John Luther Long wrote Madame Butterfly (1915 film)",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7453107833862305,
            "question": "Who directed the 1915 film adaptation of 'Madame Butterfly'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6626995205879211,
            "question": "How popular was the 1915 film adaptation of 'Madame Butterfly'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6487302184104919,
            "question": "Who wrote the story 'Madame Butterfly'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5273240208625793,
            "question": "What is the title of the story written by John Luther Long?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5093504190444946,
            "question": "Are there any other adaptations of 'Madame Butterfly' besides the 1915 film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42034912109375,
            "question": "What year was the film adaptation of 'Madame Butterfly' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22441904246807098,
            "question": "Is 'Madame Butterfly' a novel or a play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1960180103778839,
            "question": "What genre does 'Madame Butterfly' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1841413676738739,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in 'Madame Butterfly'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16052453219890594,
            "question": "Has 'Madame Butterfly' had a lasting impact on popular culture?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John Luther Long wrote Madame Butterfly (1915 film)",
            "html": "dbpedia_6913_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in 'Madame Butterfly'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6913_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre does 'Madame Butterfly' belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6913_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Madame Butterfly' a novel or a play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6913_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6913_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6913_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6913_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6913_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6913_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6913_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6913_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6913_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6913_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6913_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to document `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6913/re-ranker-msmarco/25.txt`, John Luther Long wrote the novel on which the film \"Madame Butterfly\" (1915) was based."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that the 1915 version of \"Madame Butterfly\" was based on John Luther Long's short story and was adapted into a play by David Belasco. This indicates that John Luther Long wrote the original story, which is referenced in the creation of the 1915 film, even though the document does not explicitly state it as the 1915 film itself."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Madame Butterfly (1915 film) was not written by John Luther Long, but based on his short story \"Madame Butterfly\". The original work of literature was adapted for the stage as a play by David Belasco and later used by Giacomo Puccini as the basis for his opera.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It states the 1915 film was written by John Luther Long, but the provided text clearly lists David Belasco and John Luther Long as the playwrights for the source material, not the film. Additionally, the credits for the 1915 film list Sidney Olcott and Marion Gering as directors.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}